[{"answer": "I'm doing very well.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Speaker, how are you?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "I think -- I think had the general and the president, and President Karzai had a joint appearance and said jointly this is a very unfortunate circumstance.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "So, you think it was wrong of General Allen to issue an apology then before we received an apology or the American forces received an apology for the death of the two soldiers?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "What I would have asked for is a joint appearance.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "If you were president, are you saying if this had been your situation under your watch, you would not only refuse to apologize before getting an apology from Hamid Karzai for the death of the soldiers, but you would also stop General Allen from making an apology?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Honestly, first of all, that's precisely why we better have an American energy policy.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Can you honestly continue to ramp up a rhetoric against Iran and sustain a credible argument that you would at the same time bring gas prices down to $2.50 when everybody knows the two would be inextricably linked?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, I think it would have been much better to have gone through a bankruptcy proceeding.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Where exactly do you stand out on the validity of that bailout?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "No, the -- what you had was an opportunity for the federal government to make a narrowly designed bridge loan just to get through the initial process and then allow the bankruptcy judge to implement the rules.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "So, isn't this a slight mythology about the managed bankruptcy, because the reality was the private equity money simply wasn't there to do it anyway?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Well, the reality is that the bailout has worked to some extent.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Isn't the reality that, whether you liked it or not, the bailout has worked?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, look, I think the -- the so-called devil's horn was largely a media myth.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "So the Newt Gingrich devil's horn has been put to one side and the halo is back?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Three hundred and three.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "How many nominations have you had in your history?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Have you really?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Eighty-two.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "How many times have you won?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "For the period of time, the amount of best picture nominations we have which is 20, over like 25 years, nobody's come close to that.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Can you think of anyone in history who has more nominations?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "You're 100 percent right.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Not a one.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Did you have any doubt that it would be a success?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Probably, because this is against all odds.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "If you won, would it be the most satisfying victory of your entire career, do you think?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "A black and white film; I've done plenty of movies for money.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "You didn't do it for the money?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I lost a movie that I wanted to distribute -- that I wanted to buy the script called \"Cruel Intentions.\"", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "What's the most shameless movie for money you have ever made?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "First of all, this is a movie that we found at the Tribeca Film Festival.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What do you think about it?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "This was the appeal.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "How does this work?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "I don't think we should.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "If it comes to it, could you not just edit out some of the offending F word parts of the movie?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "But the thing about Meryl Streep is she's such a sweetheart and she's loves Viola Davis.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "If she doesn't win best actress, we'll all know why, right, Harvey?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "It is true.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "All 24.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Ninety percent?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I'm going against the grain on this one and saying George Clooney.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "-- or George Clooney?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "There's not many people who could have done that role.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "And this kind of romantic thing -- I think we're 84, 85 years into the Oscars -- of a silent movie -- you've got to be a pretty good damn actor to be Oscar nominated for a silent movie, right?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Viola.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Best actress, Viola or Meryl?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Back in the day, in the '80s, and early '90s, if I can call that the day, movies like \"Raiders of The Lost Ark\" and \"E.T.\" and \"Ghost\" and \"The Fugitive\" all got nominated for best picture.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Why are they all going down this road of artsy movies which nobody really goes to watch in big numbers?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Eight or nine.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "He's done -- how many Oscars has he done?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Yes, it's not quite the same.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "It's not quite the same, is it?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "ARGER: I always like seeing Michelle Williams.", "docId": "120224pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 632}]